A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang.
Sora and Vacuum Cleaner
Sora dan Penyedot Debu
Dad bought something weird from a salesman…
Ayah membeli barang aneh dari penjual keliling…
Dad, you bought another one of those things you don't understand…
Ayah malah beli barang aneh lagi…
Well, you see…
Yah, jadi begini…
The salesman who brought this…
Penjual yang membawa ini…
was actually a cat…
ternyata seekor kucing…
Couldn't help but buy it…
Langsung terlanjur beli…
What exactly is this?
Ini benda apa sebenarnya?
You see, this is a robot vacuum…
Ini adalah robot penyedot debu loh…
And look at this!
Dan lihat ini!
It has a place for Sora to ride!
Ada tempat khusus untuk Sora duduk!
It's going to be so cute!
Pasti bakal imut!
I won't be riding the vacuum cleaner though…
Aku tidak akan naik penyedot debu itu…
Huh?
Hah?
Because it's frightening…
Keliatan seram sih…
Cleaning… Cleaning…
Sedang membersihkan… Sedang membersihkan…
It ended up that the robot vacuum is working without Sora…
Akhirnya, penyedot debu robot itu tetap bekerja tanpa Sora…
Cleaning… Cleaning…
Sedang membersihkan… Sedang membersihkan…
Cats just don't do what you want them to…
Kucing memang tidak pernah menuruti kemauan kita…
But maybe this turned out for the best…
Tapi, mungkin ini jadi yang terbaik…
It looks like Sora is most comfortable right here on my lap…
Sepertinya Sora paling nyaman justru di pangkuan ayah…
Dad seems happy about it…
Ayah tampak bahagia…
Hotori…
Hotori…
Could you hold Sora for a bit?
Bisa gendong Sora sebentar?
Dad, Sora has gotten heavy…
Ayah, Sora sudah semakin berat…
My legs have reached their limit…
Kaki ayah sudah semakin gemetaran…
Help me!
Tolong!
Just put him down yourself…
Turunkan saja sendiri…
Also, please speak normally…
Lagipula, bicaralah dengan biasa…
Sora won't ride on me again later…
Nanti Sora enggak mau naik lagi…
I highly doubt that…
Ku rasa itu tidak mungkin…
Seriously, just speak up…
Serius deh, bicara biasa saja…
Sora won't ride on me again!!
Nanti Sora tak mau naik lagi!!
Alright then…
Ya sudahlah…
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan
: geckyzz
: geckyzz